and then God said let there
然后上帝说让它在那里
be light which is the topic for this
轻装上阵 这就是我们的主题
tutorial now we want to create the look
教程现在 我们要创建外观
of a like a morning kitchen countertop
就像早晨厨房的台面一样
like you just woke up in the morning the
就像你早上刚醒来一样
sunlight's coming in and it's warm and
阳光进来了 天气很暖和
it's inviting so we want to have some
它很吸引人 所以我们想要一些
sunlight coming in uh from the left now
阳光现在从左边进来了
we could take our default lamp here and
我们可以在这里使用默认的灯 然后
turn it into a sun lamp and then try to
把它变成太阳灯 然后试着
angle it like that but the reason that
角度是这样的 但原因是
this looks so terrible is that one of
这看起来太可怕了 是其中一个
the key components of natural light is
自然光的主要成分是
not just the sunlight but the Skylight
不仅是阳光 还有天光
around it getting that uh the right
绕过它 得到那个 呃 正确的
shades of blue and white and the
蓝色和白色的阴影和
gradient as it goes towards the horizon
向地平线移动时的渐变
and that's actually quite difficult uh
而这实际上是相当困难的 嗯
to do but thankfully there's a
但谢天谢地 有一个
relatively newest feature in blender
搅拌机中相对最新的功能
which we can use so rather than uh using
我们可以这样使用 而不是呃使用
any lamp at all I'm going to delete the
任何一盏灯我都要删除
lamps so there is no light in my scene
灯光 所以我的场景中没有灯光
whatsoever and instead go to my world uh
不管怎样 去我的世界吧
tab here and then where we've got color
标签在这里 然后在哪里我们有颜色
I'm going to click the little yellow Dot
我要点击小黄点
and then select Sky texture and what
然后选择Sky纹理和其他
this is added is uh besides just the sky
这个加上的是 呃 除了天空
texture it's also added in a sunlamp so
质感也被添加到日光灯中 所以
if I rotate around we should see look at
如果我旋转一下 我们应该会看到
that real sunlight coming across it now
现在 真正的阳光照射在它上面
it is very hot by default so if you go
默认情况下很热 所以如果你去
to your render settings underneath color
设置为颜色下的渲染设置
management at the very bottom here
这里最底层的管理层
you've got an exposure slider which you
你有一个曝光滑块 你可以
use actually quite a lot um you can see
使用实际上相当多 嗯 你可以看到
the lighting has stayed the same um and
灯光一直保持不变
it doesn't have to reender anything this
它不需要对任何事情进行反驳
is purely just adjusting yeah the sensor
只是在调整传感器而已
essentially on your camera and if you
基本上是在你的相机上 如果你
hold down control uh I usually just snap
按住Ctrl 呃 我通常只会抓狂
it to a minus two now back to the sky
现在它降到了零下2度 飞回了天空
settings so what this is uh yeah
设置 所以这是什么 嗯 对
essentially it's created the exact look
基本上 它创造了一模一样的外观
of the sky a real sunlamp that little
天空中的一盏真正的太阳灯
Sun disc over there and everything will
太阳圆盘在那里 一切都会
change depending on what you set like
根据您设置的内容进行更改
the elevation right if you set it to be
如果您将其设置为正确的高程
like uh really low in the sky well
就像 嗯 非常低的天空井
that's like Morning Line you can see
这就像晨线 你可以看到
it's it's changed everything to be like
它改变了一切 就像
a warm look right so we got like really
看起来很暖和 所以我们真的
warm light over everything and if you
温暖的阳光笼罩着一切 如果你
change it to be like noon like the
把它改成像中午一样的
sunlight is coming directly above it you
阳光正从它的正上方照射过来
can see it's a lot colder and that's
可以看到天气要冷得多 那就是
because uh as the sunlight goes lower in
因为 呃 随着阳光的降低
the sky it's now passing through more of
它现在穿过的天空更多
the atmosphere so it's like decaying the
大气 所以它就像腐烂的
light and you get um yeah you get like
光 你会得到 嗯 是的 你会得到
an orangey look but as it goes more
看起来像橙色 但随着时间的推移
vertical then it's a lot more clearer
垂直的 那就清楚多了
and cleaner anyway it's a very cool
而且更干净 不管怎么说 这是一个非常酷的
setting that is uh relatively relatively
设置 呃 相对来说
new in blender um but yeah so I'm
搅拌机的新手 嗯 但是的 所以我
actually going to leave it at the
实际上我要把它留在
default at around
默认为大约
15° um the one thing I will change
15度 我要改变的一件事
though is the sun size so you get like
虽然是太阳的大小 所以你会得到
really um yeah like clean hard Shadows
真的 嗯 是的 就像干净的硬阴影
from the Sun and this sun size here the
从太阳和这里的太阳大小来看
reason for this very weird measurement
这种非常奇怪的测量方法的原因
0.545 de is because it's actually the
0.545是因为它实际上是
real Sun size in relation to the Earth
太阳相对于地球的真实大小
but there are reasons for changing that
但有理由改变这一点
because if the sun goes through through
因为如果太阳穿过
a cloud then obviously the cloud is now
云 那么很明显 云现在就是云
lighting up and it's creating more of a
点亮它 它创造了更多的
dispersed look so from the look of the
分散的看起来是如此的分散
camera I usually just adjust this to be
相机我通常只是把它调到
like a two or a three and it just makes
就像2或3 这只会让你
the Sun a little bit softer around the
太阳在太阳周围稍微柔和一点
edges um and a little nicer at least
边缘 嗯 至少更好一点
according to me awesome so looks better
对我来说太棒了 所以看起来更好
but now we have another problem which is
但现在我们有另一个问题 那就是
that the Skylight is just bleeding in um
天光之光只是在流血
from from all directions right because
来自四面八方的权利 因为
obviously it would so we need to create
显然是这样的 所以我们需要创建
an enclosure around it to obviously act
它周围的围栏显然是在表演
as an indoor space and just before we do
作为室内空间 就在我们这么做之前
that though whilst I Was preparing for
不过 在我准备的时候
this tutorial I noticed that the donuts
在这篇教程中 我注意到甜甜圈
are a little close to my backsplash here
离我的后背有点近了
and that matters because uh we're going
这很重要 因为我们要去
to use depth of field later to make
稍后使用景深制作
things that behind it are like out of
它背后的东西就像是从
focus but we can't really do that if
专注 但如果我们真的不能这样做
it's too close to the backsplash so I'm
它离挡板太近了 所以我
just going to increase the distance
只是要增加距离
there and also just scale it up a little
在那里 还可以稍微放大一点
bit because um now that it's in the
有点因为 嗯 现在它在
background
背景
um yeah otherwise you'll see like the
嗯 是的 否则你会看到就像
corners actually appear in the render
角点实际上出现在渲染中
which we which we don't want so just
我们 我们不想要的 所以只是
make that a little bit bigger move it up
把它弄大一点 再往上移一点
okay that's pretty good so essentially
好的 从本质上讲 这很好
yeah you just want to have like one two
是的 你只想要一个两个的
3ish plate widths I think will do it uh
差不多的盘子宽度 我想可以了
but yeah something like that and I also
但是 是的 类似的东西 我也
now just want to make sure ah just
现在只是想确认一下啊只是
fiddling around with this now but yeah
现在在摆弄这个 但是是的
this has got to be positioned exactly on
这个必须准确地定位在
the plate as
车牌作为
well awesome okay so that enclosure
太棒了 好的 所以那个封闭物
obviously to create that enclosure we
显然 为了创建这个围栏 我们
are going to be adding in a cube so
会加入一个立方体 所以
shift a mesh Cube and I want to scale
移动网格立方体 我想要缩放
this down because although it is like a
这是因为尽管它就像一个
kitchen right nothing outside of the
厨房就在外面 什么都没有
frame is going to be in the shot so
画面会出现在镜头中 所以
making it bigger than it needs to be is
让它变得比它需要的更大
just going to add to the render times
只是为了增加渲染时间
because then light has to bounce around
因为这样光线就会反弹
those things and yeah not good so um
那些东西 是的 不太好 所以嗯
yeah something scaled about that I don't
是啊 有些事我不知道
know something like that now uh really
我现在知道了 呃 真的
what I want it to do is just like that
我想要它做的就是这样
corner here I want it to be locked to
这里的角落 我想把它锁在
this point like I want to move it to
这一点就像我想把它移到
that point and previously in blender
这一点 以前在搅拌机
this was a really fiddly process I would
这真的是一个非常繁琐的过程
have to tap G and then Zed move along
必须轻拍G 然后Zed继续前进
that and then try and time it here and
然后试着在这里计时
then H tap G and then Y and move it and
然后H点击G 然后点击Y并移动它
it would never be exactly correct it
它永远都不会完全正确
would always just be slightly off well
总是稍微过得很好
now there is a new feature in blender
现在搅拌机有了一项新功能
literally that came in this release 4.0
从字面上看 这是在这一版本4.0中实现的
that has changed the game so there was a
这改变了比赛 所以有一个
bunch of uh snapping improvements so I
一大堆 呃 快速的改进 所以我
will show you them now so it's actually
现在就会给你们看 所以实际上
easy to understand if you just go into
很容易理解 如果您只是进入
y-frame mode so if I tap G so I'm moving
Y-Frame模式 所以如果我点击G 我就会移动
my Cube uh if you hit B it now enters
我的立方体 呃 如果你按下B 它现在进入
you into a new state called snapping
你进入了一种叫做抓拍的新状态
mode so the first thing it's asking you
所以它问你的第一件事就是
is uh what is the origin of the the
是什么 呃 是什么起源的
object that you're moving that you want
你想要移动的物体
to be the snapping point so essentially
成为如此本质上的捕捉点
as I Mouse over this you can see the
当我将鼠标移到此上方时 您可以看到
cursor is changing when it's a circle
当光标为圆形时 光标会发生变化
that means it's it it's uh going to snap
这就是说 就是它 呃 它要断了
to that face if it is a Crosshair that's
对着那张脸 如果它是一个十字准星
that edge if it's a triangle that's the
这条边如果是三角形 那就是
middle point of the edge which is
边的中点 即
sometimes useful and if it's a square
有时很有用 如果它是正方形
then that's a verticy so this is on the
然后这是垂直的 所以这是在
object that is selected right now okay
对象 现在选择该对象即可
so I obviously want that corner verticy
所以我显然想要那个垂直的角落
so I'm just going to do a single click
所以我只需点击一下
there now after I've clicked you can see
现在 在我点击之后 你可以看到
I'm able to select whichever point in
我可以选择其中任何一个点
the rest of the scene I want to snap it
场景的其余部分我想拍下来
to so just like again it's a square when
就像这样 当它是正方形的时候
it's a verticy so when I'm on these
它是垂直的 所以当我在这上面的时候
faces here uh right there I'll do a
脸在这里 呃 就在那里 我要做一个
single click and there we go so you can
点击一下 我们就开始了 这样你就可以
see it's perfectly aligned it uh with
看 它完美地与 呃 对齐了
the bottom of that uh that backsplash
那个 呃 那个靠背的底部
there now it is it is a little weird
现在就是这样 有点奇怪
I'll I'll be honest like maybe it's more
我会 我会说实话 也许这不仅仅是
weird because I've been using blender
奇怪 因为我一直在用搅拌机
for so long maybe beginners find it a
在很长一段时间里 也许初学者觉得这是一种
little bit easier but yeah like the fact
稍微容易一点 但我喜欢这个事实
that you're in a move State then you're
你处于运动状态 那么你就是
hitting B and you you you will be moving
按下B键 你就会移动
it but it's in a snapping mode rather
但它处于捕捉模式 而不是
than a a placement mode it is a little
比a a a的放置模式有点
weird and also just to make it even more
奇怪 而且只会让它变得更奇怪
complicated you can hold down alt at any
复杂的是 你可以随时按住Alt键
point and then middle Mouse to uh drag
指向然后用鼠标中键拖动
around cuz sometimes you want to snap
因为有时你想抓紧时间
like that point uh but then you need to
就像这一点 呃 但是你需要
select a point underneath an object so
选择对象下方的点 以便
you can hold down alt middle Mouse and
您可以按住Alt鼠标中键并
then uh find that point and snap it to
然后 呃 找到那个点 并抓住它
that so that's even weirder but I'm very
所以这就更奇怪了 但我非常
glad it's in there because it is great
很高兴它在里面 因为它很棒
but it is just like takes a little bit
但这就像是需要一点
to wrap your head around um but I will
把你的脑袋围起来 但我会的
continue using it actually so in face
继续使用它 其实是这样面对的
select mode in edit mode um you can see
在编辑模式中选择模式Um您可以看到
this is too high up so I can just uh I
这太高了 所以我可以
mean I could try and place it like this
意思是我可以试着把它放成这样
or I could hit B and then go this point
或者我可以敲击B 然后走到这一点
to that point same here g b this point
这一点与这一点相同
to that point yeah it's pretty pretty
在这一点上 是的 它是相当漂亮的
useful I mean it doesn't have to be this
有用 我的意思是它不一定是这样的
exact I mean this is just stuff that's
确切地说 我的意思是 这只是一些
outside of the frame but uh but anyways
在框架之外 但不管怎样
all right and I'll move this out so I do
好的 我会把这个搬出去 所以我会
need to create a little bit of space
需要创造一点空间
here cuz the camera needs to sit here
在这里 因为摄像机需要放在这里
obviously um so there needs to be a bit
显然 嗯 所以需要有一点
of space there but if I move inside you
但如果我走进你的内心
should see some flickering yay for
应该看到一些闪闪发光的YAY
flickering the flickering is because uh
一闪一闪是因为嗯
obviously the cube comes with six faces
显然 立方体有六个面
but we've already got two planes right
但我们已经有两架飞机是对的
here and we don't really need those
在这里 我们并不真的需要那些
planes we could actually map a marble
飞机我们实际上可以绘制一颗大理石
texture to the cube but then you have to
纹理到立方体 但然后你必须
deal with UV unwrapping and all that
处理UV解包和所有这些事情
stuff I find it's actually easier
我发现这其实更容易
sometimes to just work with planes um
有时候只是为了和飞机一起工作 嗯
and use that instead so instead with the
并改用它来代替
cube here I'm just going to remove the
立方体在这里 我只是要移除
two faces that I don't need so the back
两张我不需要的脸 所以后面
face and then this bottom face so
面 然后这个底面 所以
selecting those two and then hit X which
选择这两个选项 然后按X键
is another way to delete and not
是删除和不删除的另一种方式
vertices that's what we've been doing
折点 这就是我们一直在做的
currently instead hit faces so it's just
而不是打脸 所以只是
deleting those faces so now you should
删除那些面 所以现在您应该
see you have um yeah just kind of like
看 你有 嗯 对 就像
an open box four sides and then the back
一个四面打开的盒子 然后是背面
and the bottom um are open and now what
底部是打开的 现在怎么办？
I need is an opening on the left hand
我需要的是左手有个口子
side to be that window so to do that I'm
一边是那扇窗 所以我是
going to cut into it so that I get a
我要切开它 这样我就能得到
little bit of Gap um here on the left
一点点缝隙 嗯 在左边
hand side to be like the gap between the
手边要像缝隙一样
uh the wall and the window and then
呃 墙壁和窗户 然后
another Gap here between um yeah the
另一个差距是 嗯 是的
bottom of the countertop and you know so
台面的底部 你知道的
I'm going to yeah inser and for that
我要去Inser 为了那个
tool it's I so I for inser and it's now
Tool It is I so I for Inser and Now is Now
kind of like it's it's shrinking that
有点像是它在缩小
face into itself um and you're just like
面对自己 嗯 你就像是
choosing its scale essentially I'll hold
选择它的规模基本上我会坚持
down shift to get a more precise uh
调低档位以获得更精确的
movement and yeah about there that's
移动 是的 大概就是这样
pretty good and now I just delete that
很好 现在我把它删除了
face so again X and then faces awesome
再次面对X 然后面对令人敬畏的
so we should now see this which in
所以我们现在应该看到这一点
rended View mode whoops rended View mode
渲染视图模式呼喊渲染视图模式
should hopefully look
希望你能看一下
okay yeah not bad um now this window
好的 不错 嗯 现在这个窗户
frame here really is just acting like
这里的框架真的只是表现得像是
like the control for the light so if I
就像对灯光的控制 所以如果我
want I can much more precisely place
想要我能更准确地定位
this like I don't want that much light
就像我不想要那么多光一样
coming in um you know creating all that
来了 嗯 你知道 创造了所有这些
light on this side of the the wall there
墙这边的灯在那边
I can also say maybe I need more space
我也可以说 也许我需要更多的空间
here so that I've got a little bit of
在这里 我有一点
Darkness so I could put some things uh
天黑了 所以我可以把一些东西
in the background without them falling
在背景中 他们不会坠落
into light and then this bottom face
进入光芒 然后是这个底面
here sorry this bottom Edge this is
对不起 这是底边 这是
going to control where the light starts
控制灯光从哪里开始
in the scene right so if it's like all
在场景中 所以如果它像所有的
the way down here then it's uh yeah
往下走 那就是 嗯 是的
anyways you get the idea just sort of
不管怎么说 你的想法只是有点
shaping the light awesome and now with
塑造令人惊叹的光线 现在用
the camera selected I'll just move this
所选的摄像机我只需移动这个
down a little bit angle it
再往下一点角度
up there we
在那里 我们
go Al I mean you can also just do this
加油 阿尔 我是说 你也可以这么做
in um uh fly mode shift tiller key but I
在这个 呃 飞行模式下换舵把键 但是我
like hitting the uh R tool and then just
就像点击呃R工具 然后
selecting the axes and I can just tilt
选择轴线 我就可以倾斜
the camera exactly where I want it
照相机正好在我想要的地方
awesome so much better we've we've
太棒了 我们有了我们有了
controlled the Skylight so the Skylight
控制天光 使天光
is no longer coming in but we have
不再进来了 但我们有
uncontrolled Lighting in the sense that
不受控制的照明在某种意义上说
this wall here that's over here that is
这面墙 这面 这面是
supposed to represent the rest of the
被认为代表了
kitchen is hitting and receiving all of
厨房正在击打和接收所有
that sunlight light and it's just
太阳光和它只是
filling in all of this space uh on the
填写所有这些空白处 呃
right hand side and that's not good
右手边 这不太好
because we want shadow shadow is
因为我们想要的阴影是
actually a good thing it helps reveal
实际上 这是一件好事 它有助于揭示
form a lot of new artists like they get
形成了许多像他们这样的新艺术家
scared of Shadow they're try and like
害怕阴影 他们试着去喜欢
fill everything in and light everything
填满一切 点亮一切
you do want shadow shadow is a good
你真的想要影子是个好东西
thing so all this uncontrolled space is
所以所有这些不受控制的空间
not good so essentially we need to do um
不太好 所以基本上我们需要做的是
just like what you would do in the real
就像你在现实生活中所做的那样
world and that's to create a uh like
世界 那就是创造一个呃像这样的
what a photographer do they make like a
他们做的摄影师是什么样子的
a black fill card right and that's just
一张黑色的填充卡 这只是
to essentially uh stop bounce lighting
从本质上说 呃 停止反弹灯光
um from hitting this object so it's a
嗯 因为击中了这个物体 所以它是一个
good excuse to learn about a new feature
了解一项新功能的好借口
so with the cube selected if I go to the
选中立方体后 如果我转到
materials and then hit new uh we're
材料 然后打新 呃 我们是
going to keep the white material for
要把白色的材料留到
everything else right White Walls but
其他的一切都是对的 白墙
then I can add another material right
然后我就可以添加另一种材料了
underneath this one by hitting the plus
在这个下面 点击加号
button then adding another material and
按钮 然后添加另一种材料并
I'll call this one black wall and I
我会把这一面墙叫做黑墙
actually will change the Shader from
实际上会将着色器从
Principal to a much simpler uh uh
更简单的校长 嗯 嗯
diffuse it's just easier than like
扩散它比像这样容易
easier for Cycles to calculate than a
循环比一个循环更容易计算
full principled one and then this I'll
完整的原则性的 然后这个我会
just change the color to be really dark
只要把颜色改得很暗就行了
almost black all right and now in edit
几乎是黑色的 现在正在编辑中
mode I'm going to go face select and I'm
我要去选脸了 我要
going to select that one wall that I
我要选择我认为的那一面墙
want to have uh the black wall material
想要有呃黑色的墙面材料吗
to and then here I select it from the
然后在这里 我从
material list black wall and then hit
材质列表黑墙 然后点击
assign and importantly you won't see the
分配 重要的是 您将不会看到
assigned select these buttons they'll
已分配选择这些按钮 他们将
only appear when you're in edit mode so
仅当您处于编辑模式时才会显示 因此
if you don't see it it's cuz you're not
如果你看不到 那是因为你看不到
in edit mode so in edit mode um select
在编辑模式中所以在编辑模式中
the face then you'll see it and hit
然后你会看到它的脸 然后击打
assign and now look at that we have much
分配 现在看看我们有很多
more control and in fact because this
更多的控制 事实上 因为这
light uh this uh sunlight is hitting
光 呃 这个 呃 阳光正在照射
this uh this wall and it's currently
这 呃 这面墙 它目前
dark this color here now becomes almost
这里的颜色现在变得几乎变暗了
like the control for how much fill light
如控制填充光量的控件
I want on the right hand side of the
我想要在右手边
donuts so the brighter it goes the more
甜甜圈所以它越亮越好
fill light I get um yeah just a very
我得到了光 嗯 是的 只是一个非常
simple way to control that lighting a
控制照明的简单方法
bit better
好一点
awesome that's looking pretty good the
太棒了 看起来很不错
other thing I'm going to do is uh I'm
我要做的另一件事是 我
going to adjust the sun intensity so
我要调整太阳的强度 所以
there's a separate uh measurement here
这里有一个单独的呃测量
just for intensity now you could like
只是为了提高强度 现在你可能会喜欢
you could drop the intensity of um the
你可以降低这个强度
whole Sky texture as well but when you
整个天空纹理也是如此 但当您
do that it also drops the sky texture
这样做还会降低天空的纹理
right um and so I found was like for a
对 嗯 所以我发现这就像是
while when the feature came out I was
而当特写出来的时候 我正在
like trying to it was very hard to
就像试着去做一样很难
control um but I realized like if you
控制 嗯 但我意识到如果你
keep the strength at one but then you
保持一人的力量 但之后你
reduce reduce the sun intensity um you
减少日照强度嗯你
could like for example reduce the sun
例如 可以减少太阳
intensity like by a lot and then
强度很大 然后
increase your uh exposure and then it's
增加你的呃曝光率 然后它
like the sunlight is there but it's a
就像阳光在那里 但这是一种
lot softer right it's not like so
柔和多了 不是这样的
overbearing um but essentially what I
专横的嗯 但本质上我
want to do I'm going to set this sun
我要把太阳落山了
intensity to 0.5 so it's half of its
强度为0.5 所以它是它的一半
brightness but the sky texture has full
明亮 但天空的纹理已经饱满
brightness so it's just a little um yeah
亮度 所以它只是有一点 嗯 是的
a little less hot
稍微不那么热了
essentially awesome now two things I
现在基本上很棒的两件事是我
will show you before before we close
将在我们结束之前向您展示
this tutorial um which can be useful to
本教程嗯可能对以下方面有用
know one is how to import a model okay
知道一个是如何导入模型好吗？
because although as a beginner it's good
因为尽管作为一个初学者
to understand modeling tools and know
了解建模工具并了解
how to build things uh when you start
当你开始的时候 呃 如何建造东西
building scenes it's very common
建筑场景是很常见的
professional artists in studios to just
演播室里的专业艺术家
make use of model libraries because
使用模型库 因为
there is so much you need to model and
有太多的东西你需要建模和
basically fill in to create a realistic
基本上都是填上来创造一个逼真的
believable scene it's just too much for
可信的场景 这对我来说太难了
one artist to do so it's very common to
一位艺术家这样做是很常见的
make use of model libraries
利用模型库
so what I want you to do is click the
所以我想让你做的是点击
link in the description and you will
描述中的链接 您将
find this model the wood utensils which
找到这个型号的木制器皿
we're going to put in the background is
我们要做的背景是
a free model and it's available in
免费模型 可在
multiple softwares the one we're looking
我们正在寻找的多个软件
for is the blender file so hit download
因为是搅拌机文件 所以点击下载
on that and then just like before unzip
然后就像之前一样解压
the file that you receive and inside it
您收到并保存在其中的文件
you should see a bunch of textures and
您应该会看到一堆纹理和
then one do blend file then we're going
然后一个Do Blend文件 然后我们就去
to go to file you would think import but
要进入文件 你会认为是重要的 但
actually this is for um external file
实际上 这是用于这个外部文件的
extensions like not blend files if you
扩展名 如不混合文件 如果
want to import a blend file it's
想要导入混合文件 它是
actually the append option okay so now
实际上 追加选项好的 所以现在
we select that blend file double click
我们选择该混合文件 双击
it and now we're actually reading the
现在我们实际上是在阅读
blend file we're reading the information
Blend文件我们正在读取信息
inside that blend file and it's saying
在该混合文件中 它说
what do you want to import do you want
您想要导入什么？
to import just a single object from that
要从中仅导入单个对象 请执行以下操作
blend file do you want to import uh you
混合文件是否要导入 呃 您
know a texture or a material perhaps but
也许知道一种纹理或一种材料 但
in a lot of cases if it's just a blend
在很多情况下 如果它只是一种混合物
file that contains like one model it's
包含一个模型的文件
often going to in a collection a single
经常在一个集合中使用一首单曲
collection so go into collection and
集合 因此进入集合并
then just click the one that's there and
然后只需点击那里的那个
then hit append and now even though
然后点击追加 现在即使
there is multiple objects as part of
有多个对象作为的一部分
this um it's just brought in all of them
这个 嗯 它刚刚把他们所有的人都带来了
and it's put it into a collection
它把它放进了一个收藏中
already utensils jar
餐具已经放在罐子里了
001 so now I'm just going to move this
所以现在我要把这个
into the back of my scene and that's it
在我的场景后面 就是这样
so that's how to import data from one
这就是如何从一个
blend file into another it's going a
将文件混合到另一个文件中它将成为
little slow for me I'm going to move
对我来说有点慢 我要走了
that there we go so I just want it yeah
我们就这样走了 所以我只想要它
somewhere in the background like that
就在这样的背景下
the other thing I want to show you how
另一件事我想向你们展示
to do is how to install an add-on
要做的是如何安装外接程序
because although you might think that's
因为尽管你可能认为这是
kind of like an advanced user thing you
有点像是高级用户的事情
will very quickly realize that a lot of
很快就会意识到很多
workflows rely on add-ons so add-ons are
工作流依赖于加载项 因此加载项
very powerful and there's a lot of them
非常强大 而且他们有很多人
out there and it's not actually clear
但实际上并不清楚
how to install add-ons to beginners so I
如何为初学者安装插件 以便我
thought I would include that so
我想我应该把它包括进去 所以
obviously we're going to use the uh the
显然 我们将使用呃
polygon add-on I mentioned this uh this
Polygon Add-on我提到了这个 这个
earlier it just lets you like download
早些时候 它只是让你喜欢下载
and import objects with uh with one
和进口物品 呃 用一个
click and there's a bunch of free models
点击 这里有一堆免费的模特
in here as well well so you can actually
在这里也是如此 所以你实际上可以
get started with those and and do some
开始做这些 然后做一些
interesting things click the link in the
有趣的事情点击链接
description this will take you to the
说明这将把您带到
download page and you just looking to
下载页面 而您只是在寻找
download that great so you can see it's
下载那个很棒的 这样你就可以看到
uh downloaded a single zip file and
UH下载了一个单独的压缩文件并
importantly you do not want to unzip
重要的是 您不想解压缩
that zip file and the reason is is that
这个压缩文件的原因是
blender installs add-ons from the zip
Blender安装压缩包中的附加组件
file that is unextracted so to install
未解压缩的文件 以便安装
an add-on you go to edit preferences
用于编辑首选项的附加组件
add-ons and then at the top click on
附加组件 然后在顶部单击
install then Loc where you downloaded
安装 然后定位您下载的位置
the zip file just that there and then
压缩文件就在那里 然后
you just hit install and now if it's
您只需点击安装 现在如果它是
correct if it's like found and located
如果它类似于找到并定位 则更正
uh and add-on inside that zip file it
以及压缩文件中的附加组件
should then automatically take you to
然后会自动将您带到
the name of that add-on uh in the search
搜索中加载项的名称
so you just have it there and then to
所以你只要把它放在那里 然后
enable it you just do a single click to
启用它您只需点击一下即可
check it and it's now enabled now
选中它 它现在已启用
obviously every atom will have a
显然每个原子都会有一个
different way of accessing it but
访问它的方式不同 但
commonly they are in the sidebar which
通常 它们位于侧边栏中
is exactly where the polygon one is so
就是多边形的位置
you'll see the tab here they might
你会在这里看到标签 他们可能会
actually be changing the sidebar some
实际上是在改变侧边栏的一些
point in the future but for now this is
点在未来 但现在这是
uh anyway how it is um so then just go
呃 不管怎么样 嗯 那就走吧
login via browser it's going to take you
通过浏览器登录将需要您
to the website it'll say login confirmed
到网站 它会显示登录已确认
return back to the add-on uh and you can
返回到附加组件 呃 您可以
type in free and you can see um a whole
免费输入 你可以看到整个
bunch of different assets there so
那里有一堆不同的资产
actually one that I will uh import if I
实际上 我会呃进口的 如果我
go to my model section and then go to
转到我的模特区 然后转到
vegetation there's a bunch of different
植被有很多不同之处
plants here um there's like four free
这里的植物 嗯 好像有四个免费的
ones I believe so you can use one of
我相信 所以你可以使用其中之一
those I'm going to be using a paid one
我要用的是付费的
just this uh SP one I thought looked
只有这个 呃 SP 我觉得看起来像
quite nice but yeah you can access one
挺好的 但是你可以访问一个
of these these free ones if you want to
这些免费的 如果你想的话
and there we go awesome so this is our
我们很棒 所以这是我们的
render we are nearing the Finish Line I
我们正在接近终点线I
can feel it we're getting close so join
可以感觉到我们已经越来越接近了 所以加入吧
me in the next part we're going to dive
我下一部分我们要潜水
into the composition and then animation
进入构图 然后动画
and then the final render so click here
然后是最终的渲染 所以单击此处
and I'll see you there
我们在那里见